<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Neil Gandhi</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/</link><description>Recent content on Neil Gandhi</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 09:32:43 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.realdealneil.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Securing ASP .NET Core Apps Made Easy</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/secure-headers-asp-net/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 09:32:43 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/secure-headers-asp-net/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->








&lt;img src="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/secure-headers-asp-net/hacker_hu16312857404512943086.png" alt="Hacker Acting Maliciously" loading="lazy">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Whether you like it or not, there are best practices for security that web applications need to follow. 👋 Today, I want to chat about a nifty little library that can make your ASP.NET Core applications more secure with minimal effort. Say hello to &lt;strong>&lt;a href="https://github.com/andrewlock/NetEscapades.AspNetCore.SecurityHeaders">NetEscapades.AspNetCore.SecurityHeaders&lt;/a>&lt;/strong>!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Track Home Repairs Easily with Google Sheets</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/track-home-repairs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 12:01:49 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/track-home-repairs/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;/p>








&lt;img src="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/track-home-repairs/home-repairs_hu9019918320357220400.png" alt="LED TV" loading="lazy">
&lt;p>If you&amp;rsquo;re a homeowner and as your home ages, repairs will become common. Often, you need to go back to see when you did a repair or what kind of warranty the repair had. Keeping track of home repairs and improvements can be a daunting task, but using a &lt;a href="https://sheets.google.com">Google Sheets&lt;/a> spreadsheet can make it much easier.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Brighten Up Your TV Experience with LED Light Strips</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/led-light-strip-tv/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 19:01:14 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/led-light-strip-tv/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;/p>








&lt;img src="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/led-light-strip-tv/tv_hu8093855570406518441.png" alt="LED TV" loading="lazy">
&lt;p>Ever feel like your TV setup could use a little extra pizzazz? Well, I&amp;rsquo;ve got a super cost-effective upgrade that can make a &lt;strong>huge difference&lt;/strong> in your viewing experience: &lt;strong>LED light strips&lt;/strong>! 🌈&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="why-led-light-strips">Why LED Light Strips?&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>First off, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about the &lt;strong>cost&lt;/strong>. LED light strips are incredibly affordable. You can snag a decent set for under $20, and trust me, the bang for your buck is phenomenal. Compared to other home theater upgrades, this is a steal! This is a simple upgrade that provides a dramatic improvement.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Monorepo or Multi-Repo? Why Not a Metarepo!</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/use-git-metarepo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 12:17:47 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/use-git-metarepo/</guid><description>&lt;p>In the software development world, there&amp;rsquo;s always a debate about whether to use monorepos or multi-repos. Each has its pros and cons, but what if you could get the best of both worlds? Enter the metarepo. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive into what a metarepo is, why it&amp;rsquo;s awesome, and how you can set one up.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="whats-a-metarepo">What&amp;rsquo;s a Metarepo?&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>A metarepo, or meta-repository, is like a master repo that holds references to other repos. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t contain the actual code but acts as a central hub. This way, you can manage multiple repos as if they were one, striking a balance between monorepo and multi-repo setups.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Use Drivvo to Maintain Your Car</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/use-drivvo-car-manager/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 18:56:24 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/use-drivvo-car-manager/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hey there, fellow productivity enthusiasts! Ever feel like there should be an easier way to manage your vehicle? Between tracking fuel expenses, scheduling maintenance, and keeping tabs on all those little costs, it can get overwhelming. But what if I told you there&amp;rsquo;s an app that can handle all that for you, making your life a whole lot easier? Enter &lt;a href="https://www.drivvo.com/">&lt;strong>Drivvo&lt;/strong>&lt;/a> – your new best friend for vehicle management.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Creating a Bash Alias for Visual Git Diffs</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/bash-alias-git-diff/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 16:16:40 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/bash-alias-git-diff/</guid><description>&lt;p>While I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of using Git from the CLI, there are some things that are better with a GUI. If you&amp;rsquo;re a developer who frequently uses Git and TortoiseGit, you might find it handy to create a Bash alias that opens the TortoiseGit diff window directly from the command line. This can save you time and streamline your workflow. In this post, I&amp;rsquo;ll guide you through the steps to create a Bash alias called &lt;code>git-diff&lt;/code> that does just that.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Boost Productivity with a Clipboard Manager</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/use-clipboard-manager/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 15:48:22 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/use-clipboard-manager/</guid><description>&lt;p>In the fast-paced world of software development and digital work, efficiency is key. One often-overlooked tool that can significantly enhance your productivity is a clipboard manager. If you frequently copy and paste text, images, or other data, a clipboard manager can streamline your workflow and save you valuable time. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how a clipboard manager can improve your productivity and why &lt;a href="https://ditto-cp.sourceforge.io/">Ditto&lt;/a> is an excellent choice for Windows users.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Using Shortcodes in Hugo to Resize Images</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/hugo-resize-image/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 20:15:20 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/hugo-resize-image/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hugo is a powerful static site generator that offers a lot of flexibility through its templating system. One of the features that makes Hugo so versatile is the ability to create and use shortcodes. In this post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how to create a shortcode to resize images and use it in your content pages.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="why-use-shortcodes-for-image-resizing">Why Use Shortcodes for Image Resizing?&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Imagine you&amp;rsquo;re creating multiple blog posts and need to resize images to fit onto each page. You could whip up your favorite photo editor, but why not take advantage of Hugo&amp;rsquo;s built-in image resizing? Unfortunately, it can&amp;rsquo;t be used directly on your content pages without &lt;em>shortcodes&lt;/em>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/about/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://www.realdealneil.com/images/personal-photo_hu14014629973969522278.jpg" alt="Personal Photo" loading="lazy">
&lt;p>Hi there! I’m a passionate software engineer with a journey that began back in 10th grade when I wrote my first lines of code. Since then, my fascination with technology has only grown, leading me to explore various programming languages, frameworks, and tools.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Over the years, I’ve honed my skills in languages like Node.js and C#, and delved into the intricacies of application architecture and Kubernetes. My professional experience has equipped me with a solid foundation in system design and problem-solving, ensuring that the software I develop is both robust and efficient.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>