<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Programming on Neil Gandhi</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/tags/programming/</link><description>Recent content in Programming on Neil Gandhi</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.realdealneil.com/tags/programming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Make VS Code Smarter with GitLens!</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-gitlens-to-boost-productivity/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-gitlens-to-boost-productivity/</guid><description>&lt;p>In the realm of software development, understanding the history of your codebase is paramount. Knowing who changed what, when, and why can significantly enhance your productivity and streamline your workflow. Enter &lt;a href="https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=eamodio.gitlens">&lt;strong>GitLens&lt;/strong>&lt;/a>, an incredibly powerful and versatile extension for &lt;a href="https://code.visualstudio.com/">Visual Studio Code (VS Code)&lt;/a> that takes your &lt;a href="https://git-scm.com/">Git&lt;/a> experience to the next level.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="what-is-gitlens">What is GitLens?&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>GitLens supercharges the Git capabilities built into VS Code. It enables developers to gain deeper insights into their codebase through various features like blame annotations, commit details, code lens, and more. By bringing historical context and repository information right into your editor, GitLens transforms the way you interact with your code.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Painless Exception Monitoring With Sentry</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/exception-monitoring-with-sentry/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/exception-monitoring-with-sentry/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;/p>











&lt;img src="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/exception-monitoring-with-sentry/frustrated-software-tester_hu1834766650273423161.png" alt="Frustrated Software Tester" loading="lazy">

&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced development environment, ensuring the stability and reliability of your applications is paramount. One of the most effective ways to achieve this is through &lt;strong>exception monitoring&lt;/strong>. This practice not only helps in identifying and resolving issues quickly but also enhances the overall quality and user experience of your software.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In my early engineering career, I used email to capture exceptions from our applications. Obviously, it became overwhelming and inefficient quickly! After some time, I adopted dedicated monitoring tools like &lt;a href="https://sentry.io/">&lt;strong>Sentry&lt;/strong>&lt;/a> which brought immediate and significant productivity benefits for myself and my teams. The benefits of these tools may not initially be obvious, but once it&amp;rsquo;s adopted across an organization, it reduces many inefficiencies that team members weren&amp;rsquo;t even aware of.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>