<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Neil Gandhi</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/tags/home/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Neil Gandhi</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.realdealneil.com/tags/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Trick to Finding Cheap Holiday Gifts for the Kids!</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/12/easy-affordable-kids-christmas-gifts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/12/easy-affordable-kids-christmas-gifts/</guid><description>&lt;p>Ah, the joy of Christmas shopping! The twinkling lights, the cheerful carols, and of course, the stress of finding the perfect gifts for the kids in your life. Fear not, dear reader, because I have a fantastic trick up my sleeve that will save you time, money, and maybe even a few gray hairs: &lt;strong>&lt;a href="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/deal-alerts-for-home-staples">deal alerts on Slickdeals&lt;/a>&lt;/strong>!&lt;/p>
&lt;h4 id="the-magic-of-deal-alerts">The Magic of Deal Alerts&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/deal-alerts-for-home-staples">I previously discussed&lt;/a> how deal alerts on Slickdeals can be an excellent way to save on home staples which you&amp;rsquo;ll inevitably need. During the holiday seasons, finding gifts for kids is inevitable. When it comes to shopping for toys, Slickdeals is your ultimate Santa&amp;rsquo;s helper. By turning on deal alerts for toys, you&amp;rsquo;ll be the first to know when those must-have items go on sale.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Hidden Benefits of Cashback Sites for Travel</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/11/use-cashback-sites-for-travel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/11/use-cashback-sites-for-travel/</guid><description>&lt;p>Traveling can be one of life’s greatest pleasures, but it’s no secret that it often comes with a hefty price tag. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re booking a flight, reserving a hotel, or renting a car, the costs can add up quickly. Many travelers instinctively book directly with airlines or hotels, believing this is the best way to secure the lowest rates and best service. However, this common perception overlooks a powerful tool for savings: &lt;a href="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-cashback-sites-for-extra-savings/">cashback sites&lt;/a>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Bright Side of Electric Toothbrushes: Why They’re Worth Every Penny</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/get-shiny-teeth-with-electric-toothbrushes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/get-shiny-teeth-with-electric-toothbrushes/</guid><description>&lt;p>When it comes to oral hygiene, everyone wants to have that million-dollar smile. One of the most effective ways to achieve this is by switching to an electric toothbrush. A few years ago a dental hygenist recommended I get an electric toothbrush, even a budget brand, and praised the benefits. I dove in and haven&amp;rsquo;t regretted it since. While the initial cost may be slightly higher than a conventional toothbrush, the long-term benefits make it a worthy investment.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Fuel Up Your Savings: How Upside Turns Gas Purchases into Cashback</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/get-easy-cashback-with-upside/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/get-easy-cashback-with-upside/</guid><description>&lt;p>Let’s be honest – filling up your gas tank isn’t exactly the highlight of your week. But what if I told you there’s a way to make this routine expense a little more rewarding? Enter &lt;a href="https://www.upside.com/">&lt;strong>Upside&lt;/strong>&lt;/a>, an app that turns your everyday gas purchases into easy cashback. I&amp;rsquo;m a huge fan of using &lt;a href="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-cashback-sites-for-extra-savings">cashback sites&lt;/a> to get money back for purchases you were already going to make. Why not do the same thing with your gas purchases!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Roborock Robot Vacuums are a Modern Home Essential!</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/get-a-roborock-vacuum/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/get-a-roborock-vacuum/</guid><description>&lt;p>There are a few times in my life where I was blown away by a piece of technology. My first robot vacuum purchase in 2017 was one of those. At that time, I decided to take a deep dive into robot vacuums. After many years of hearing about them, I felt the time was right and smarts in the technology were ready for wide adoption. After pouring into my research, I purchased a Xiaomi Mi Vacuum. This was an international Chinese vacuum which made me a little hesitant, but the buzz behind it was incredible. Turned out, it was well deserved.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Maximize Savings with Cashback Sites like Rakuten</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-cashback-sites-for-extra-savings/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-cashback-sites-for-extra-savings/</guid><description>&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s world, who doesn&amp;rsquo;t love a good deal? With online shopping becoming more ubiquitous, the quest for savings is more relevant than ever. Previously, I discussed how you can find easy coupon codes with &lt;a href="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-retailmenot-to-save-big">RetailMeNot&lt;/a>. But one of the most effective ways to save money while shopping online is through cashback sites like Rakuten. If you&amp;rsquo;re not familiar with how these platforms work, buckle up. You’re about to find out how you can make every purchase count and put some cash back into your pocket.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Unlock Savings with RetailMeNot When Online Shopping</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-retailmenot-to-save-big/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 14:47:25 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-retailmenot-to-save-big/</guid><description>&lt;p>Online shopping has become a staple for many of us. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re buying clothes, electronics, or groceries, there&amp;rsquo;s always a way to save a little extra. One of the best tools to help you do this is &lt;a href="https://www.retailmenot.com/">&lt;strong>RetailMeNot&lt;/strong>&lt;/a>. This platform is a treasure trove of coupon codes and deals for a wide range of online stores. Often, you&amp;rsquo;ll find coupon codes to save more on items you were already going to buy! Let&amp;rsquo;s dive into the benefits of using RetailMeNot and how you can make the most of it with their handy &lt;a href="https://chromewebstore.google.com/detail/retailmenot-codes-cash-ba/jjfblogammkiefalfpafidabbnamoknm">Chrome extension&lt;/a>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Save Big With Amazon Prime Credit Card!</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/save-big-with-amazon-prime-credit-card/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/save-big-with-amazon-prime-credit-card/</guid><description>&lt;p>\&lt;/p>











&lt;img src="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/save-big-with-amazon-prime-credit-card/browsing-amazon-with-credit-card_hu13853732918785188299.png" alt="Person browsing Amazon.com with a credit card in hand" loading="lazy">

&lt;p>Hey there, fellow Amazon enthusiast! If you&amp;rsquo;re already an Amazon Prime member, you&amp;rsquo;re probably enjoying all the perks like free two-day shipping, Prime Video, and more. But did you know there&amp;rsquo;s a way to save even more money on your Amazon purchases? Enter the &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Prime-Visa/dp/BT00LN946S">&lt;strong>Amazon Prime Credit Card&lt;/strong>&lt;/a>. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive into why this card is a no-brainer for frequent Amazon shoppers.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="5-cash-back-on-amazon-purchases">5% Cash Back on Amazon Purchases&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>First things first, the &lt;strong>5% cash back&lt;/strong> on all &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com">Amazon.com&lt;/a> purchases is a game-changer. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re buying the latest tech gadgets, stocking up on household essentials, or treating yourself to some new books, that 5% adds up quickly. Think about it: every time you make a purchase, you&amp;rsquo;re essentially getting a 5% discount. Over time, this can lead to significant savings, especially if you&amp;rsquo;re a frequent shopper.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Get Grubhub+ With Amazon Prime!</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/get-grubhub-with-amazon-prime/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/get-grubhub-with-amazon-prime/</guid><description>&lt;p>\&lt;/p>











&lt;img src="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/get-grubhub-with-amazon-prime/delivery-driver_hu14426926147184321514.png" alt="Driver delivering food from his car" loading="lazy">

&lt;p>If you&amp;rsquo;re an &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/amazonprime">Amazon Prime&lt;/a> member, there&amp;rsquo;s a new perk you won&amp;rsquo;t want to miss: &lt;strong>&lt;a href="https://www.aboutamazon.com/news/retail/amazon-prime-grubhub">Grubhub+ is now available for free&lt;/a>&lt;/strong> with your membership! This exciting announcement means you can enjoy all the benefits of &lt;a href="https://www.grubhub.com/plus">Grubhub+&lt;/a> without any additional cost, making your Prime membership even more valuable. Previously, this perk was available for one-year, but as of June 25, 2024, it&amp;rsquo;s now included with Amazon Prime with no limits.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Use Slickdeals Alerts to Save Big on Household Staples</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/deal-alerts-for-home-staples/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:38:35 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/deal-alerts-for-home-staples/</guid><description>&lt;p>\&lt;/p>











&lt;img src="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/deal-alerts-for-home-staples/slickdeals-homepage_hu14556206072624881742.png" alt="Slickdeals Homepage" loading="lazy">

&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced world, finding the best deals on everyday home staples can be a game-changer for your budget. &lt;a href="https://www.slickdeals.net">Slickdeals&lt;/a>, a popular deal-sharing community, offers a powerful feature called &lt;a href="https://slickdeals.net/deal-alerts/">Deal Alerts&lt;/a> that can help you snag great discounts on items you use regularly. Here&amp;rsquo;s how practical it is to create these alerts and maximize your savings.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="what-is-slickdeals">What is Slickdeals?&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.slickdeals.net">Slickdeals&lt;/a> is a deal-sharing community. If there&amp;rsquo;s a deal on any product from any store out there, this community will find it and post to their forums. There&amp;rsquo;s an upvoting feature to vote on the hottest deals. The best of the best become Frontpage deals that show on the landing page. I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Slickdeals for over 15 years and it&amp;rsquo;s a core part of my internet experience!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Replace Your Windshield Wipers Without Breaking The Bank</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/get-quality-windshield-wipers-easily/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 11:27:57 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/get-quality-windshield-wipers-easily/</guid><description>&lt;p>\&lt;/p>











&lt;img src="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/get-quality-windshield-wipers-easily/driving-in-rain_hu14145931693425104582.png" alt="Car Driving in Downpour" loading="lazy">

&lt;p>During my recent state vehicle inspection, they flagged my windshield wipers as needing replacement. They wouldn&amp;rsquo;t pass my inspection until I provided proof that it was replaced, or let them replace it. Of course, it&amp;rsquo;s a common tactic to make easy money. Windshield wipers are ridiculously easy to replace and you should always do it yourself.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>One thing holding me back in the past was the cost. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t justify replacing windshield wipers every year when they ran up to $30 for a pair. Or pay less for a budget pair which wouldn&amp;rsquo;t take long to start streaking on your windshields.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Track Home Repairs Easily with Google Sheets</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/track-home-repairs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 12:01:49 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/track-home-repairs/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;br>











&lt;img src="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/track-home-repairs/home-repairs_hu9019918320357220400.png" alt="LED TV" loading="lazy">
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you&amp;rsquo;re a homeowner and as your home ages, repairs will become common. Often, you need to go back to see when you did a repair or what kind of warranty the repair had. Keeping track of home repairs and improvements can be a daunting task, but using a &lt;a href="https://sheets.google.com">Google Sheets&lt;/a> spreadsheet can make it much easier.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This method allows you to maintain a detailed history of all the work done on your home, including information about contractors, dates, costs, and warranties. As a homeowner, this will come in handy when inevitably you need to look at what kind of warranty you had on a part or which contractor you used before. Here’s how you can set it up and the benefits it offers.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Brighten Up Your TV Experience with LED Light Strips</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/led-light-strip-tv/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 19:01:14 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/led-light-strip-tv/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;br>











&lt;img src="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/led-light-strip-tv/tv_hu8093855570406518441.png" alt="LED TV" loading="lazy">
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Ever feel like your TV setup could use a little extra pizzazz? Well, I&amp;rsquo;ve got a super cost-effective upgrade that can make a &lt;strong>huge difference&lt;/strong> in your viewing experience: &lt;strong>LED light strips&lt;/strong>! 🌈&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="why-led-light-strips">Why LED Light Strips?&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>First off, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about the &lt;strong>cost&lt;/strong>. LED light strips are incredibly affordable. You can snag a decent set for under $20, and trust me, the bang for your buck is phenomenal. Compared to other home theater upgrades, this is a steal! This is a simple upgrade that provides a dramatic improvement.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Use Drivvo to Maintain Your Car</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/use-drivvo-car-manager/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 18:56:24 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/use-drivvo-car-manager/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hey there, fellow productivity enthusiasts! Ever feel like there should be an easier way to manage your vehicle? Between tracking fuel expenses, scheduling maintenance, and keeping tabs on all those little costs, it can get overwhelming. But what if I told you there&amp;rsquo;s an app that can handle all that for you, making your life a whole lot easier? Enter &lt;a href="https://www.drivvo.com/">&lt;strong>Drivvo&lt;/strong>&lt;/a> – your new best friend for vehicle management.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="what-is-drivvo-">What is Drivvo? 🚗💡&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.drivvo.com/">Drivvo&lt;/a> is a comprehensive vehicle management app (&lt;a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=br.com.ctncardoso.ctncar">Android&lt;/a>, &lt;a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/drivvo-car-management/id1206041425">iOS&lt;/a>) designed to help you keep track of everything related to your car, motorcycle, or truck. From fuel expenses to maintenance schedules, Drivvo has got you covered. And the best part? It&amp;rsquo;s super easy to use! I&amp;rsquo;ve used Drivvo for years and it&amp;rsquo;s invaluable for keeping track of my regular car maintenance.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>