<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Neil Gandhi</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Neil Gandhi</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Get Cleaner Teeth With a Water Flosser!</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/get-cleaner-teeth-with-water-flosser/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/get-cleaner-teeth-with-water-flosser/</guid><description>&lt;p>Oral hygiene is crucial for maintaining overall health, and flossing is a key part of this routine. While traditional floss has been a staple in dental care for decades, water flossers are gaining popularity as a modern alternative. A few years ago I made a switch to water flossers and I was genuinely surprised at much it improved my teeth. I don&amp;rsquo;t say that in jest either. My dental cleaning appointments became much faster and I noticed less time spent cleaning out plaque and tartar. The hygenists also noticed an improvement in my teeth and commented on how clean they are.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Make VS Code Smarter with GitLens!</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-gitlens-to-boost-productivity/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-gitlens-to-boost-productivity/</guid><description>&lt;p>In the realm of software development, understanding the history of your codebase is paramount. Knowing who changed what, when, and why can significantly enhance your productivity and streamline your workflow. Enter &lt;a href="https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=eamodio.gitlens">&lt;strong>GitLens&lt;/strong>&lt;/a>, an incredibly powerful and versatile extension for &lt;a href="https://code.visualstudio.com/">Visual Studio Code (VS Code)&lt;/a> that takes your &lt;a href="https://git-scm.com/">Git&lt;/a> experience to the next level.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="what-is-gitlens">What is GitLens?&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>GitLens supercharges the Git capabilities built into VS Code. It enables developers to gain deeper insights into their codebase through various features like blame annotations, commit details, code lens, and more. By bringing historical context and repository information right into your editor, GitLens transforms the way you interact with your code.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Roborock Robot Vacuums are a Modern Home Essential!</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/get-a-roborock-vacuum/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/get-a-roborock-vacuum/</guid><description>&lt;p>There are a few times in my life where I was blown away by a piece of technology. My first robot vacuum purchase in 2017 was one of those. At that time, I decided to take a deep dive into robot vacuums. After many years of hearing about them, I felt the time was right and smarts in the technology were ready for wide adoption. After pouring into my research, I purchased a Xiaomi Mi Vacuum. This was an international Chinese vacuum which made me a little hesitant, but the buzz behind it was incredible. Turned out, it was well deserved.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Maximize Savings with Cashback Sites like Rakuten</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-cashback-sites-for-extra-savings/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-cashback-sites-for-extra-savings/</guid><description>&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s world, who doesn&amp;rsquo;t love a good deal? With online shopping becoming more ubiquitous, the quest for savings is more relevant than ever. Previously, I discussed how you can find easy coupon codes with &lt;a href="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-retailmenot-to-save-big">RetailMeNot&lt;/a>. But one of the most effective ways to save money while shopping online is through cashback sites like Rakuten. If you&amp;rsquo;re not familiar with how these platforms work, buckle up. You’re about to find out how you can make every purchase count and put some cash back into your pocket.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Unlock Savings with RetailMeNot When Online Shopping</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-retailmenot-to-save-big/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 14:47:25 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-retailmenot-to-save-big/</guid><description>&lt;p>Online shopping has become a staple for many of us. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re buying clothes, electronics, or groceries, there&amp;rsquo;s always a way to save a little extra. One of the best tools to help you do this is &lt;a href="https://www.retailmenot.com/">&lt;strong>RetailMeNot&lt;/strong>&lt;/a>. This platform is a treasure trove of coupon codes and deals for a wide range of online stores. Often, you&amp;rsquo;ll find coupon codes to save more on items you were already going to buy! Let&amp;rsquo;s dive into the benefits of using RetailMeNot and how you can make the most of it with their handy &lt;a href="https://chromewebstore.google.com/detail/retailmenot-codes-cash-ba/jjfblogammkiefalfpafidabbnamoknm">Chrome extension&lt;/a>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Why Password Managers Are A Must Have</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-a-password-manager/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-a-password-manager/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;/p>











&lt;img src="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-a-password-manager/Bitwarden-multiple-devices_hu10378902343542409610.webp" alt="Screenshots of BitWarden across multiple device types" loading="lazy">

&lt;p>&lt;em>Screenshot from &lt;a href="https://www.bitwarden.com">https://www.bitwarden.com&lt;/a>&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, managing passwords can be a daunting task. With the increasing number of online accounts, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to maintain strong, unique passwords for each one. Yet, many people avoid using password managers for no good reason, often relying on weak, easily guessable passwords or reusing the same password across multiple sites. This practice is a recipe for disaster, leading to potential identity theft and account breaches. Amongst the alternatives, I recommend most people adopt &lt;a href="https://bitwarden.com/">BitWarden&lt;/a> as their password manager of choice.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Boost Browser Productivity with CrxMouse for Chrome</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-crxmouse-gestures/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-crxmouse-gestures/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;/p>











&lt;img src="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-crxmouse-gestures/engineer-with-mouse_hu4308584055936015338.png" alt="Software engineer at desktop using mouse furiously" loading="lazy">

&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced digital world, efficiency is key. As a software engineer, you know the importance of optimizing every aspect of your workflow. One tool that can significantly enhance your browsing experience is the &lt;a href="https://crxmouse.com/">CrxMouse&lt;/a> &lt;a href="https://chromewebstore.google.com/detail/crxmouse-mouse-gestures/jlgkpaicikihijadgifklkbpdajbkhjo">extension for Chrome&lt;/a>. This powerful extension leverages mouse gestures to streamline your web navigation, making your browsing more productive and efficient.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="what-is-crxmouse">What is CrxMouse?&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://crxmouse.com/">CrxMouse&lt;/a> is a &lt;a href="https://chromewebstore.google.com/detail/crxmouse-mouse-gestures/jlgkpaicikihijadgifklkbpdajbkhjo">Chrome extension&lt;/a> that supercharges your web experience with intuitive mouse gestures. Instead of relying solely on keyboard shortcuts or multiple clicks, you can perform various actions with simple hand movements. This not only saves time but also reduces the cognitive load associated with remembering numerous shortcuts.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Save Big With Amazon Prime Credit Card!</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/save-big-with-amazon-prime-credit-card/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/save-big-with-amazon-prime-credit-card/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;/p>











&lt;img src="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/save-big-with-amazon-prime-credit-card/browsing-amazon-with-credit-card_hu13853732918785188299.png" alt="Person browsing Amazon.com with a credit card in hand" loading="lazy">

&lt;p>Hey there, fellow Amazon enthusiast! If you&amp;rsquo;re already an Amazon Prime member, you&amp;rsquo;re probably enjoying all the perks like free two-day shipping, Prime Video, and more. But did you know there&amp;rsquo;s a way to save even more money on your Amazon purchases? Enter the &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Prime-Visa/dp/BT00LN946S">&lt;strong>Amazon Prime Credit Card&lt;/strong>&lt;/a>. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive into why this card is a no-brainer for frequent Amazon shoppers.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Painless Exception Monitoring With Sentry</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/exception-monitoring-with-sentry/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/exception-monitoring-with-sentry/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;/p>











&lt;img src="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/exception-monitoring-with-sentry/frustrated-software-tester_hu1834766650273423161.png" alt="Frustrated Software Tester" loading="lazy">

&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced development environment, ensuring the stability and reliability of your applications is paramount. One of the most effective ways to achieve this is through &lt;strong>exception monitoring&lt;/strong>. This practice not only helps in identifying and resolving issues quickly but also enhances the overall quality and user experience of your software.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In my early engineering career, I used email to capture exceptions from our applications. Obviously, it became overwhelming and inefficient quickly! After some time, I adopted dedicated monitoring tools like &lt;a href="https://sentry.io/">&lt;strong>Sentry&lt;/strong>&lt;/a> which brought immediate and significant productivity benefits for myself and my teams. The benefits of these tools may not initially be obvious, but once it&amp;rsquo;s adopted across an organization, it reduces many inefficiencies that team members weren&amp;rsquo;t even aware of.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Get Grubhub+ With Amazon Prime!</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/get-grubhub-with-amazon-prime/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/get-grubhub-with-amazon-prime/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;/p>











&lt;img src="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/get-grubhub-with-amazon-prime/delivery-driver_hu14426926147184321514.png" alt="Driver delivering food from his car" loading="lazy">

&lt;p>If you&amp;rsquo;re an &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/amazonprime">Amazon Prime&lt;/a> member, there&amp;rsquo;s a new perk you won&amp;rsquo;t want to miss: &lt;strong>&lt;a href="https://www.aboutamazon.com/news/retail/amazon-prime-grubhub">Grubhub+ is now available for free&lt;/a>&lt;/strong> with your membership! This exciting announcement means you can enjoy all the benefits of &lt;a href="https://www.grubhub.com/plus">Grubhub+&lt;/a> without any additional cost, making your Prime membership even more valuable. Previously, this perk was available for one-year, but as of June 25, 2024, it&amp;rsquo;s now included with Amazon Prime with no limits.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Elevate Your Team Screenshot Productivity with ShareX</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/use-sharex-for-screenshots/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 12:39:50 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/use-sharex-for-screenshots/</guid><description>&lt;p>It&amp;rsquo;s common for software engineering teams to rely on screenshot and screen recording tools. It&amp;rsquo;s used to build documentation, bug reporting, and various other day-to-day activities. However, many organizations invest in commercial tools like &lt;a href="https://www.techsmith.com/snagit/">SnagIt&lt;/a> with hefty licenses. Or don&amp;rsquo;t take advantage of productivity features that many of these tools offer. It&amp;rsquo;s time to revisit screenshots and learn how to invest in cost-effective solutions and take advantage of the robust productivity features which are commonly overlooked!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Use Slickdeals Alerts to Save Big on Household Staples</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/deal-alerts-for-home-staples/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:38:35 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/deal-alerts-for-home-staples/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;/p>











&lt;img src="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/deal-alerts-for-home-staples/slickdeals-homepage_hu14556206072624881742.png" alt="Slickdeals Homepage" loading="lazy">

&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced world, finding the best deals on everyday home staples can be a game-changer for your budget. &lt;a href="https://www.slickdeals.net">Slickdeals&lt;/a>, a popular deal-sharing community, offers a powerful feature called &lt;a href="https://slickdeals.net/deal-alerts/">Deal Alerts&lt;/a> that can help you snag great discounts on items you use regularly. Here&amp;rsquo;s how practical it is to create these alerts and maximize your savings.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="what-is-slickdeals">What is Slickdeals?&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.slickdeals.net">Slickdeals&lt;/a> is a deal-sharing community. If there&amp;rsquo;s a deal on any product from any store out there, this community will find it and post to their forums. There&amp;rsquo;s an upvoting feature to vote on the hottest deals. The best of the best become Frontpage deals that show on the landing page. I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Slickdeals for over 15 years and it&amp;rsquo;s a core part of my internet experience!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Replace Your Windshield Wipers Without Breaking The Bank</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/get-quality-windshield-wipers-easily/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 11:27:57 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/get-quality-windshield-wipers-easily/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;/p>











&lt;img src="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/get-quality-windshield-wipers-easily/driving-in-rain_hu14145931693425104582.png" alt="Car Driving in Downpour" loading="lazy">

&lt;p>During my recent state vehicle inspection, they flagged my windshield wipers as needing replacement. They wouldn&amp;rsquo;t pass my inspection until I provided proof that it was replaced, or let them replace it. Of course, it&amp;rsquo;s a common tactic to make easy money. Windshield wipers are ridiculously easy to replace and you should always do it yourself.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>One thing holding me back in the past was the cost. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t justify replacing windshield wipers every year when they ran up to $30 for a pair. Or pay less for a budget pair which wouldn&amp;rsquo;t take long to start streaking on your windshields.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Securing ASP .NET Core Apps Made Easy</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/secure-headers-asp-net/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 09:32:43 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/secure-headers-asp-net/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->











&lt;img src="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/secure-headers-asp-net/hacker_hu16312857404512943086.png" alt="Hacker Acting Maliciously" loading="lazy">
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Whether you like it or not, there are best practices for security that web applications need to follow. 👋 Today, I want to chat about a nifty little library that can make your ASP.NET Core applications more secure with minimal effort. Say hello to &lt;strong>&lt;a href="https://github.com/andrewlock/NetEscapades.AspNetCore.SecurityHeaders">NetEscapades.AspNetCore.SecurityHeaders&lt;/a>&lt;/strong>!&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="the-problem-security-headers">The Problem: Security Headers&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>If you&amp;rsquo;ve been working with web applications for a while, you know that security is a big deal. One common way to enhance security is by adding security headers to your HTTP responses. These headers can help protect against a variety of attacks, like cross-site scripting (XSS) and clickjacking. However, manually configuring these headers can be a bit of a hassle. You have to remember which headers to add, what values to set, and ensure they&amp;rsquo;re applied consistently across your app.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Track Home Repairs Easily with Google Sheets</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/track-home-repairs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 12:01:49 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/track-home-repairs/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;/p>











&lt;img src="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/track-home-repairs/home-repairs_hu9019918320357220400.png" alt="LED TV" loading="lazy">

&lt;p>If you&amp;rsquo;re a homeowner and as your home ages, repairs will become common. Often, you need to go back to see when you did a repair or what kind of warranty the repair had. Keeping track of home repairs and improvements can be a daunting task, but using a &lt;a href="https://sheets.google.com">Google Sheets&lt;/a> spreadsheet can make it much easier.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This method allows you to maintain a detailed history of all the work done on your home, including information about contractors, dates, costs, and warranties. As a homeowner, this will come in handy when inevitably you need to look at what kind of warranty you had on a part or which contractor you used before. Here’s how you can set it up and the benefits it offers.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Brighten Up Your TV Experience with LED Light Strips</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/led-light-strip-tv/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 19:01:14 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/led-light-strip-tv/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;/p>











&lt;img src="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/led-light-strip-tv/tv_hu8093855570406518441.png" alt="LED TV" loading="lazy">

&lt;p>Ever feel like your TV setup could use a little extra pizzazz? Well, I&amp;rsquo;ve got a super cost-effective upgrade that can make a &lt;strong>huge difference&lt;/strong> in your viewing experience: &lt;strong>LED light strips&lt;/strong>! 🌈&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="why-led-light-strips">Why LED Light Strips?&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>First off, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about the &lt;strong>cost&lt;/strong>. LED light strips are incredibly affordable. You can snag a decent set for under $20, and trust me, the bang for your buck is phenomenal. Compared to other home theater upgrades, this is a steal! This is a simple upgrade that provides a dramatic improvement.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Monorepo or Multi-Repo? Why Not a Metarepo!</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/use-git-metarepo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 12:17:47 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/use-git-metarepo/</guid><description>&lt;p>In the software development world, there&amp;rsquo;s always a debate about whether to use monorepos or multi-repos. Each has its pros and cons, but what if you could get the best of both worlds? Enter the metarepo. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive into what a metarepo is, why it&amp;rsquo;s awesome, and how you can set one up.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="whats-a-metarepo">What&amp;rsquo;s a Metarepo?&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>A metarepo, or meta-repository, is like a master repo that holds references to other repos. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t contain the actual code but acts as a central hub. This way, you can manage multiple repos as if they were one, striking a balance between monorepo and multi-repo setups.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Use Drivvo to Maintain Your Car</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/use-drivvo-car-manager/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 18:56:24 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/use-drivvo-car-manager/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hey there, fellow productivity enthusiasts! Ever feel like there should be an easier way to manage your vehicle? Between tracking fuel expenses, scheduling maintenance, and keeping tabs on all those little costs, it can get overwhelming. But what if I told you there&amp;rsquo;s an app that can handle all that for you, making your life a whole lot easier? Enter &lt;a href="https://www.drivvo.com/">&lt;strong>Drivvo&lt;/strong>&lt;/a> – your new best friend for vehicle management.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="what-is-drivvo-">What is Drivvo? 🚗💡&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.drivvo.com/">Drivvo&lt;/a> is a comprehensive vehicle management app (&lt;a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=br.com.ctncardoso.ctncar">Android&lt;/a>, &lt;a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/drivvo-car-management/id1206041425">iOS&lt;/a>) designed to help you keep track of everything related to your car, motorcycle, or truck. From fuel expenses to maintenance schedules, Drivvo has got you covered. And the best part? It&amp;rsquo;s super easy to use! I&amp;rsquo;ve used Drivvo for years and it&amp;rsquo;s invaluable for keeping track of my regular car maintenance.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Creating a Bash Alias for Visual Git Diffs</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/bash-alias-git-diff/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 16:16:40 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/bash-alias-git-diff/</guid><description>&lt;p>While I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of using Git from the CLI, there are some things that are better with a GUI. If you&amp;rsquo;re a developer who frequently uses Git and TortoiseGit, you might find it handy to create a Bash alias that opens the TortoiseGit diff window directly from the command line. This can save you time and streamline your workflow. In this post, I&amp;rsquo;ll guide you through the steps to create a Bash alias called &lt;code>git-diff&lt;/code> that does just that.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Boost Productivity with a Clipboard Manager</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/use-clipboard-manager/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 15:48:22 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/use-clipboard-manager/</guid><description>&lt;p>In the fast-paced world of software development and digital work, efficiency is key. One often-overlooked tool that can significantly enhance your productivity is a clipboard manager. If you frequently copy and paste text, images, or other data, a clipboard manager can streamline your workflow and save you valuable time. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how a clipboard manager can improve your productivity and why &lt;a href="https://ditto-cp.sourceforge.io/">Ditto&lt;/a> is an excellent choice for Windows users.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Using Shortcodes in Hugo to Resize Images</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/hugo-resize-image/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 20:15:20 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/hugo-resize-image/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hugo is a powerful static site generator that offers a lot of flexibility through its templating system. One of the features that makes Hugo so versatile is the ability to create and use shortcodes. In this post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how to create a shortcode to resize images and use it in your content pages.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="why-use-shortcodes-for-image-resizing">Why Use Shortcodes for Image Resizing?&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Imagine you&amp;rsquo;re creating multiple blog posts and need to resize images to fit onto each page. You could whip up your favorite photo editor, but why not take advantage of Hugo&amp;rsquo;s built-in image resizing? Unfortunately, it can&amp;rsquo;t be used directly on your content pages without &lt;em>shortcodes&lt;/em>.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>