<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Productivity on Neil Gandhi</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/tags/productivity/</link><description>Recent content in Productivity on Neil Gandhi</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.realdealneil.com/tags/productivity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Automatically Mark Archived Emails as Read</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2025/01/archive-and-mark-as-read-gmail/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2025/01/archive-and-mark-as-read-gmail/</guid><description>&lt;p>Gmail introduced the now universal concept of archiving emails. This let you remove emails from your inbox, yet not completely delete them in case you needed to retrieve an email at a later time. Frequently, you archive an email without even opening it when the subject tells you all you need to know.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Unfortunately, this means you end up with unread emails in your archive. Gmail doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a feature to mark as read and archive in one fail swoop. However, there is a clever trick to help automate this process.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Make VS Code Smarter with GitLens!</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-gitlens-to-boost-productivity/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-gitlens-to-boost-productivity/</guid><description>&lt;p>In the realm of software development, understanding the history of your codebase is paramount. Knowing who changed what, when, and why can significantly enhance your productivity and streamline your workflow. Enter &lt;a href="https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=eamodio.gitlens">&lt;strong>GitLens&lt;/strong>&lt;/a>, an incredibly powerful and versatile extension for &lt;a href="https://code.visualstudio.com/">Visual Studio Code (VS Code)&lt;/a> that takes your &lt;a href="https://git-scm.com/">Git&lt;/a> experience to the next level.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="what-is-gitlens">What is GitLens?&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>GitLens supercharges the Git capabilities built into VS Code. It enables developers to gain deeper insights into their codebase through various features like blame annotations, commit details, code lens, and more. By bringing historical context and repository information right into your editor, GitLens transforms the way you interact with your code.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Why Password Managers Are A Must Have</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-a-password-manager/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-a-password-manager/</guid><description>&lt;p>\&lt;/p>











&lt;img src="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-a-password-manager/Bitwarden-multiple-devices_hu10378902343542409610.webp" alt="Screenshots of BitWarden across multiple device types" loading="lazy">

&lt;p>&lt;em>Screenshot from &lt;a href="https://www.bitwarden.com">https://www.bitwarden.com&lt;/a>&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, managing passwords can be a daunting task. With the increasing number of online accounts, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to maintain strong, unique passwords for each one. Yet, many people avoid using password managers for no good reason, often relying on weak, easily guessable passwords or reusing the same password across multiple sites. This practice is a recipe for disaster, leading to potential identity theft and account breaches. Amongst the alternatives, I recommend most people adopt &lt;a href="https://bitwarden.com/">BitWarden&lt;/a> as their password manager of choice.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Boost Browser Productivity with CrxMouse for Chrome</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-crxmouse-gestures/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-crxmouse-gestures/</guid><description>&lt;p>\&lt;/p>











&lt;img src="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/10/use-crxmouse-gestures/engineer-with-mouse_hu4308584055936015338.png" alt="Software engineer at desktop using mouse furiously" loading="lazy">

&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced digital world, efficiency is key. As a software engineer, you know the importance of optimizing every aspect of your workflow. One tool that can significantly enhance your browsing experience is the &lt;a href="https://crxmouse.com/">CrxMouse&lt;/a> &lt;a href="https://chromewebstore.google.com/detail/crxmouse-mouse-gestures/jlgkpaicikihijadgifklkbpdajbkhjo">extension for Chrome&lt;/a>. This powerful extension leverages mouse gestures to streamline your web navigation, making your browsing more productive and efficient.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="what-is-crxmouse">What is CrxMouse?&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://crxmouse.com/">CrxMouse&lt;/a> is a &lt;a href="https://chromewebstore.google.com/detail/crxmouse-mouse-gestures/jlgkpaicikihijadgifklkbpdajbkhjo">Chrome extension&lt;/a> that supercharges your web experience with intuitive mouse gestures. Instead of relying solely on keyboard shortcuts or multiple clicks, you can perform various actions with simple hand movements. This not only saves time but also reduces the cognitive load associated with remembering numerous shortcuts.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Save Big With Amazon Prime Credit Card!</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/save-big-with-amazon-prime-credit-card/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/save-big-with-amazon-prime-credit-card/</guid><description>&lt;p>\&lt;/p>











&lt;img src="https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/save-big-with-amazon-prime-credit-card/browsing-amazon-with-credit-card_hu13853732918785188299.png" alt="Person browsing Amazon.com with a credit card in hand" loading="lazy">

&lt;p>Hey there, fellow Amazon enthusiast! If you&amp;rsquo;re already an Amazon Prime member, you&amp;rsquo;re probably enjoying all the perks like free two-day shipping, Prime Video, and more. But did you know there&amp;rsquo;s a way to save even more money on your Amazon purchases? Enter the &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Prime-Visa/dp/BT00LN946S">&lt;strong>Amazon Prime Credit Card&lt;/strong>&lt;/a>. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive into why this card is a no-brainer for frequent Amazon shoppers.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="5-cash-back-on-amazon-purchases">5% Cash Back on Amazon Purchases&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>First things first, the &lt;strong>5% cash back&lt;/strong> on all &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com">Amazon.com&lt;/a> purchases is a game-changer. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re buying the latest tech gadgets, stocking up on household essentials, or treating yourself to some new books, that 5% adds up quickly. Think about it: every time you make a purchase, you&amp;rsquo;re essentially getting a 5% discount. Over time, this can lead to significant savings, especially if you&amp;rsquo;re a frequent shopper.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Elevate Your Team Screenshot Productivity with ShareX</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/use-sharex-for-screenshots/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 12:39:50 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/use-sharex-for-screenshots/</guid><description>&lt;p>It&amp;rsquo;s common for software engineering teams to rely on screenshot and screen recording tools. It&amp;rsquo;s used to build documentation, bug reporting, and various other day-to-day activities. However, many organizations invest in commercial tools like &lt;a href="https://www.techsmith.com/snagit/">SnagIt&lt;/a> with hefty licenses. Or don&amp;rsquo;t take advantage of productivity features that many of these tools offer. It&amp;rsquo;s time to revisit screenshots and learn how to invest in cost-effective solutions and take advantage of the robust productivity features which are commonly overlooked!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Use Drivvo to Maintain Your Car</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/use-drivvo-car-manager/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 18:56:24 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/use-drivvo-car-manager/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hey there, fellow productivity enthusiasts! Ever feel like there should be an easier way to manage your vehicle? Between tracking fuel expenses, scheduling maintenance, and keeping tabs on all those little costs, it can get overwhelming. But what if I told you there&amp;rsquo;s an app that can handle all that for you, making your life a whole lot easier? Enter &lt;a href="https://www.drivvo.com/">&lt;strong>Drivvo&lt;/strong>&lt;/a> – your new best friend for vehicle management.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="what-is-drivvo-">What is Drivvo? 🚗💡&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.drivvo.com/">Drivvo&lt;/a> is a comprehensive vehicle management app (&lt;a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=br.com.ctncardoso.ctncar">Android&lt;/a>, &lt;a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/drivvo-car-management/id1206041425">iOS&lt;/a>) designed to help you keep track of everything related to your car, motorcycle, or truck. From fuel expenses to maintenance schedules, Drivvo has got you covered. And the best part? It&amp;rsquo;s super easy to use! I&amp;rsquo;ve used Drivvo for years and it&amp;rsquo;s invaluable for keeping track of my regular car maintenance.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Creating a Bash Alias for Visual Git Diffs</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/bash-alias-git-diff/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 16:16:40 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/bash-alias-git-diff/</guid><description>&lt;p>While I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of using Git from the CLI, there are some things that are better with a GUI. If you&amp;rsquo;re a developer who frequently uses Git and TortoiseGit, you might find it handy to create a Bash alias that opens the TortoiseGit diff window directly from the command line. This can save you time and streamline your workflow. In this post, I&amp;rsquo;ll guide you through the steps to create a Bash alias called &lt;code>git-diff&lt;/code> that does just that.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Boost Productivity with a Clipboard Manager</title><link>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/use-clipboard-manager/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 15:48:22 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.realdealneil.com/posts/2024/09/use-clipboard-manager/</guid><description>&lt;p>In the fast-paced world of software development and digital work, efficiency is key. One often-overlooked tool that can significantly enhance your productivity is a clipboard manager. If you frequently copy and paste text, images, or other data, a clipboard manager can streamline your workflow and save you valuable time. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how a clipboard manager can improve your productivity and why &lt;a href="https://ditto-cp.sourceforge.io/">Ditto&lt;/a> is an excellent choice for Windows users.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>